<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><metadata>
    <idinfo>
        <citation>
            <citeinfo>
                <title>cityclerk_nma_nhoods_main</title>
                <geoform>vector digital data</geoform>
            </citeinfo>
        </citation>
        <descript>
            <abstract>Neighborhood map atlas district areas are derived from the Seattle City Clerk's Office Neighborhood Map Atlas.  These are the largest neighborhood areas and have been supplemented with alternate names from other sources in 2020.  They are subdivided further into the neighborhood map atlas sub-areas called neighborhoods.  The sub-neighborhoods field contains a comma delimited list of all the sub-areas and their alternate names.The original atlas is designed for subject indexing of legislation, photographs, and other documents and is an unofficial delineation of neighborhood boundaries used by the City Clerks Office. Sources for this atlas and the neighborhood names used in it include a 1980 neighborhood map produced by the Department of Community Development, Seattle Public Library indexes, a 1984-1986 Neighborhood Profiles feature series in the Seattle Post-Intelligencer, numerous parks, land use and transportation planning studies, and records in the Seattle Municipal Archives. Many of the neighborhood names are traditional names whose meaning has changed over the years, and others derive from subdivision names or elementary school attendance areas.</abstract>
            <purpose>Neighborhood map atlas district areas are derived from the Seattle City Clerk's Office Neighborhood Map Atlas.  These are the largest neighborhood areas and have been supplemented with alternate names from other sources.</purpose>
        </descript>
        <timeperd>
            <timeinfo>
                <sngdate>
                    <caldate>20110101</caldate>
                </sngdate>
            </timeinfo>
            <current>publication date</current>
        </timeperd>
        <status>
            <progress>Complete</progress>
            <update>None planned</update>
        </status>
        <spdom>
            <bounding>
                <westbc>-122.438158</westbc>
                <eastbc>-122.235677</eastbc>
                <northbc>47.735878</northbc>
                <southbc>47.493342</southbc>
            </bounding>
        </spdom>
        <keywords>
            <theme>
                <themekt>None</themekt>
                <themekey>Neighborhood</themekey>
            </theme>
        </keywords>
        <accconst>Public.</accconst>
        <useconst>Reproduction or distribution of GIS data for commercial purposes is prohibited, unless expressly authorized through a separate licensing agreement with The City of Seattle.</useconst>
        <ptcontac>
            <cntinfo>
                <cntorgp>
                    <cntorg>Seattle Public Utilities</cntorg>
                    <cntper>Albert Gonzales</cntper>
                </cntorgp>
                <cntpos>GIS Products &amp; Services Supervisor</cntpos>
                <cntaddr>
                    <addrtype>mailing</addrtype>
                    <address>700 5th Ave, Suite 4900</address>
                    <city>Seattle</city>
                    <state>WA</state>
                    <postal>98124-4018</postal>
                </cntaddr>
                <cntvoice>206-684-7887</cntvoice>
                <cntfax>206-684-8914</cntfax>
                <cntemail>albert.gonzales@seattle.gov</cntemail>
            </cntinfo>
        </ptcontac>
        <datacred/>
        <native>Esri ArcGIS 12.6.2.24783</native>
    </idinfo>
    <spdoinfo>
        <direct>Vector</direct>
        <ptvctinf>
            <sdtsterm>
                <sdtstype>GT-polygon composed of chains</sdtstype>
                <ptvctcnt>0</ptvctcnt>
            </sdtsterm>
        </ptvctinf>
    </spdoinfo>
    <eainfo>
        <detailed>
            <enttyp>
                <enttypl>cityclerk_nma_nhoods_main</enttypl>
            </enttyp>
            <attr>
                <attrlabl>OBJECTID</attrlabl>
                <attrdef>Internal feature number.</attrdef>
                <attrdefs>ESRI</attrdefs>
                <attrdomv>
                                        
                    <udom>Sequential unique whole numbers that are automatically generated.</udom>
                                    
                </attrdomv>
            </attr>
            <attr>
                <attrlabl>L_HOOD</attrlabl>
            </attr>
            <attr>
                <attrlabl>SHAPE</attrlabl>
                <attrdef>Feature geometry.</attrdef>
                <attrdefs>ESRI</attrdefs>
                <attrdomv>
                                        
                    <udom>Coordinates defining the features.</udom>
                                    
                </attrdomv>
            </attr>
            <attr>
                <attrlabl>Shape_Length</attrlabl>
                <attrdef>Length of feature in internal units.</attrdef>
                <attrdefs>Esri</attrdefs>
                <attrdomv>
                                        
                    <udom>Positive real numbers that are automatically generated.</udom>
                                    
                </attrdomv>
            </attr>
            <attr>
                <attrlabl>Shape_Area</attrlabl>
                <attrdef>Area of feature in internal units squared.</attrdef>
                <attrdefs>Esri</attrdefs>
                <attrdomv>
                                        
                    <udom>Positive real numbers that are automatically generated.</udom>
                                    
                </attrdomv>
            </attr>
        </detailed>
    </eainfo>
    <metainfo>
        <metd>20201201</metd>
        <metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
        <metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
        <mettc>local time</mettc>
    </metainfo>
</metadata>
